Most of us know that the risk of getting ill is reduced when we look after ourselves.
我们大多数人都知道，当我们照顾好自己时，生病的风险就会降低。
Taking regular exercise has proven to be good for our health and scientists have found that the risk of cancer and heart disease is reduced when we take part in physical activity — and now they‘ve found cycling to work is one of the best activities to do this.
事实证明，经常锻炼对我们的健康有益，科学家们发现，当我们参加体育活动时，患癌症和心脏病的风险会降低——现在他们发现，骑自行车上班是实现这一目标的最佳活动之一。
Well, good news for me then!
嗯，那对我来说可是个好消息！
The biggest study into the issue linked the use of two wheels with a halving of the risk of cancer and heart disease.
关于这个问题的最大规模研究显示，骑自行车可使患癌症和心脏病的风险减半。
The five- year study of 250,000 UK commuters also showed walking had some benefits over sitting on public transport or taking the car.
这项对25万名英国通勤者进行的为期五年的研究还表明，相比乘坐公共交通工具或开车，步行更有益处。
Pedalling to work is already popular in many cities across the world.
骑自行车上班在世界上许多城市已经很流行了。
Some forward- thinking authorities have built cycle lanes to make the commute safer, as well as providing secure places to lock them up.
一些有前瞻性思维的当局修建了自行车道，以使通勤更安全，同时还提供了安全的停车锁车的地方。
Some companies also provide facilities for their employees to get changed and cleaned up when they arrive at work.
一些公司还为员工提供设施，让他们在上班时可以换衣服和洗漱。
It all makes good sense - according to people surveyed in this study, regular cycling cut the risk of death from any cause by 41%, the incidence of cancer by 45% and heart disease by 46%.
这一切都很有道理——根据这项研究中的调查对象所说，经常骑自行车可使各种原因导致的死亡风险降低41%，患癌症的几率降低45%，患心脏病的几率降低46%。
For me, cycling to work is quicker and cheaper than using public transport and it‘s my only form of exercise.
对我来说，骑自行车上班比乘坐公共交通工具更快、更便宜，而且这是我唯一的锻炼方式。
And whereas going to the gym to lose a few pounds takes effort and commitment, cycling has just become part of the work routine.
而去健身房减肥需要付出努力和坚持，骑自行车却已经成为我工作日常的一部分。
Clare Hyde from Cancer Research UK says “This study helps to highlight the potential benefits of building activity into your everyday life.
英国癌症研究中心的克莱尔·海德说：“这项研究有助于强调将活动融入日常生活的潜在好处。
Anything that gets you a bit hot and out of breath ... can help make a difference.”
任何让你有点发热、气喘吁吁的活动……都能有所帮助。”
Of course, any exercise is good for you but it‘s thought that cycling is better than walking because the activity is longer and more intense.
当然，任何运动都对你有好处，但人们认为骑自行车比步行更好，因为骑自行车的活动时间更长、强度更大。
Dr Jason Gill, from the University of Glasgow, told the BBC “You need to get to work every day so if you built cycling into the day it essentially takes willpower out of the equation.”
格拉斯哥大学的杰森·吉尔博士告诉BBC：“你每天都需要去上班，所以如果你把骑自行车融入到日常生活中，这基本上就不需要意志力了。”
For me, it’s the best and most enjoyable workout I can have - and I don‘t need to wear skin- tight lycra clothes, as long as I wear the most important accessory, a helmet.
对我来说，这是我能进行的最好、最令人愉快的锻炼——而且我不需要穿紧身的莱卡运动服，只要戴上最重要的配饰——头盔就行了。